Kateryna Pysova

Junior Frontend Developer with the insatiable desire to learn and apply what has been learned. My educational background has helped me to develop a strategic mindset, along with decent time management skills and the ability to digest large volumes of technical information under short periods





katepysova97@gmail.com

Amsterdam, Netherlands

+380501829221

in linkedin.com/in/kateryna-pysova-b7871718b

EDUCATION

Master's degree in Applied Mathematics

Odessa I.I. Mechnikov National University

09/2019 - 12/2020

Odessa, Ukraine

Bachelor's degree in Applied Mathematics Odessa I.I. Mechnikov National University

09/2015 - 07/2019 Odessa, Ukraine

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Frontend Developer SteelKiwi Development

11/2021 - 08/2022

Odessa, Ukraine

Steelkiwi Inc. is an American outsourcing company that develops websites and mobile applications.

Intern-Trainee Frontend Developer SteelKiwi Development

05/2021 - 10/2021

Odessa, Ukraine

Steelkiwi Inc. is an American outsourcing company that develops websites and mobile applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

CSS/SCSS/SASS

Git/GitHub

EsLint/StyleLint/Prettier

PERSONAL PROJECTS

https://github.com/katepysova

CERTIFICATES

EF SET English Certificate 64/100 (C1 Advanced)

https://www.efset.org/cert/RZbpPG

Version Control with GIT

https://shorturl.at/dlW46

Build Responsive Real World Websites with HTML5 and CSS3

https://shorturl.at/mpSV8

Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations and More!

https://shorturl.at/BEHTX

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Russian

Full Professional Proficiency

Ukrainian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency